Our new president is here.
Chou and Max took advantage of the opportunity.
Yi-Yi Hsia, employee of the Shengli Group.
Make a good impression.
Hello, Mr. Zhou.
What if the president has a crush on her?
What can they do?
what's going on?
Yi-Yi Hsia, it's you again.
Director of Planning
Hurry up and give this new product to the customers.
Every day, all I know is.
boot-licking
Mr. Zhou
This is Mr. Wang.
Evidence of corruption and bribery
abnormal
too much makeup
Mr. Zhou
It's all because my men don't know what they're doing. Look.
This is what I have for you.
And you're having an affair.
Embezzlement of public funds and nepotism
You're fired.
Monster President
Corporate assholes.
Perseverance. Dreams.
None of it.
Get lost!
How can you, Grandma Chow?
Grandma Chow and Sieve
Just came to put
Grandma Zhou
Grandma Zhou and Sieve
Grandma Zhou, an old employee of the company
Grandma Zhou and Grandma Sieve
They're all open.
(coll.) boobies
That kind of trash stays in the company to raise rice worms to play with you?
An Zixuan
Miss Xingyu Group
It's horrible.
An Zi Chicory
Miss Xingyu Group.
That's us, Shenghe.
The parachuted-in president.
straightforward
It's our director.
Is he the devil?
It's good to get out of here so he doesn't keep giving you a hard time.
Oh, yeah.
You're looking for me again?
Of course it is.
Anzisa (name)
You've got a meal.
I've lost two months' salary again.
After me, I'll be drinking the northwest wind. I'm the Miss An of Xingyu Group.
I'll be able to make my sisters drink the wind.
lit. either you are good or you steal (idiom); either you are good or you steal
Miss Anne.
You won't be.
You want me to do it for you again?
Let's go on a blind date.
Yes, with Grandma Chau.
Grandma Chau and Max.
I've arranged a blind date for you tonight.
She's the daughter of the Star Island Group.